now to get more on this we want to go to
the de nuts 2016 campaign headquarters
uh in AA to check in with the campaign
[Music]
manager thanks Larry Mike Yard uh you're
the de nuts campaign manager yep let me
tell you something when I heard about
this story last night I quit the show
and flew out the Iowa
Larry sometimes you just got to follow
your heart man and in this case I got to
follow Disney
n wait you have to you're willing to
throw away a career in television to go
work on a political campaign because it
has a funny name hell yeah I'm excited
Larry this is a once- in a-lifetime
opportunity and if you listen to my
candidate stance on entitlement reform
he's I'm just kidding we're talking
about these
nuts what more do you want from a person
running for president in 2016
ideas for how to make America better man
you sound like Martin no
Ali that dude is pulling at 2% Larry you
know why name nonrecognition nobody
cares about anything he has to say
because his name is boring okay wake me
up when you want to talk about these
nuts
okay Larry Larry Larry oh oh oh hey hey
it's let's go to Ricky VES who's
covering the social media angle from the
night we show D hey Ricky
I'm here following this phenomenon and
you should see these Larry you need to
see this uh these what these
nuts all right all right you got me you
got me this is really catching on Larry
it looks like everyone's really pulling
for these NS okay
Ricky Ricky you're not giving me any
information I think you're just having
fun saying these nuts no no I'm not
Larry you know you know I take my work
very seriously here let me read this to
you there's a report that says these
nuts are blowing up all over Twitter
these nuts are all over Instagram and
they're busting all over your
face Facebook Facebook page Larry oh
um all you're doing is making a joke out
of these nuts R these what these nuts no
now you got me saying
it
lar yeah you got me you got me Larry
Larry
Larry can I interject here oh yes of
course Holly Walker
everybody okay uh she's coming to us
from the council for women's voting go
ahead Holly Larry this is the most
juvenile thing I have ever seen thank
you yes I agree once again all of our
political discourse is dominated by
males in their locker room sensibilities
we're not having conversation about the
issues that matter exactly Holly that's
my point Thank you thank you all right
so who who's the candidate you're most
interested in talking about okay Larry
there is a very exciting Dark Horse out
of Pennsylvania she's a female candidate
who has a lot to say that's that's great
what's her name her name is De
titties I can't believe this Holly now
you're doing it too no Larry I am
completely serious these TT ass sprang
out of
nowhere yeah
how is that serious serious Larry listen
listen the campaign was sagging but now
they're starting to pick
up and they're getting a lot of
support her pole numbers are lifting and
separating through the swing
states that doesn't even make sense oh
my God Mike Y what are you doing there I
thought you were working with these nuts
I was until I heard about these
tities Larry Larry sorry I'm getting
some information that these nuts and
these toes are now joining forces I
already know I already know okay I've
had enough of this mik colie and Ricky
everybody we'll be right
[Applause]
back